vroom.com 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy                                                                                                                            Last Updated: January 12, 2018
    We are committed to protecting the personal information that you share with us. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as it sets forth our practices
    regarding the information we collect from you and your options to limit our use and disclosure of your information. If you need to pull over and call for
    service, email us at support@vroom.com
1. Scope and Your Consent
This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to the tools, features, and services (collectively, the “Services”) offered by Vroom, Inc., or its wholly owned
subsidiaries, such as Left Gate Property Holding, LLC d/b/a Texas Direct Auto (together, “Vroom”, “we”, or “our”), through any Vroom website or mobile site,
including, without limitation, Vroom, Texas Direct Auto, Texas Direct Auto Auction, and Sell Us Your Car (together, “Sites”) and web-based and mobile
applications (“Apps”) that reference or link to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into Vroom’s Terms of Use (“Terms”). Capitalized terms not
defined in the Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms.
This Privacy Policy covers:
• Information collected from those who use our Services (“you” or “your”); and
• Information that our Business Partners (defined below) share with Vroom or that we share with our Business Partners.
You accept and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy when you (a) create an Account with Vroom and/or (b) access or use one or all of the Services that link to
this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of: (i) third-party individuals or entities who perform tasks on our behalf (“Service Providers”); (ii) our
third-party business partners who provide websites, applications or other products or services that you may encounter or access through the Services (“Business
Partners”); or (iii) any other third parties (collectively with Service Providers and Business Partners, “Third Parties”), even if you access, encounter or interact with
such Third Parties through the Services. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Parties that share our respect for your privacy, we are not
responsible for the privacy policies or practices of Third Parties, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Parties’ privacy policies.
2. Information Collected or Received
When you use the Services, Vroom may collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personally Identifiable Information” (defined below) (collectively, “Information”)
about you, your use of the Services, or the device you use to access the Services.
A. Non-Personal Information
“Non-Personal Information” is any information that does not enable identification of an individual, such as, without limitation, technical information, behavioral
information, and aggregated information, including service usage information, web traffic information, content viewed on the Services, your preferences, and
information about your operating system, browser, device, keyboard language and hardware.
B. Personally Identifiable Information
“Personally Identifiable Information” (or “PII”) is information that identifies you. Examples of PII that may be collected through the Services include, without
limitation:
• Name
• Email address
• Mailing address
• Telephone number(s)

• Login information
• Social networking handle or username
• Photos (e.g., for profiles)
• Date of birth
• Social security number
• Driver’s license state and number
• Financial information
• Employment information
• Residency or credit proof information (e.g., utility bill, copy of paystub, references)
• Insurance information
The specific Information actually collected by Vroom will depend on the portion of the Services you access. If Non-Personal Information is connected or linked to PII,
we treat the Non-Personal Information as PII.
3. How We Collect Information
    We collect Information that is provided by you voluntarily, collected automatically through the Services, or provided by Third Parties.
A. PII Provided Directly by You
You may voluntarily provide us with PII when using the Services, including, without limitation, when you perform the following activities:
• Register for an Account or create a profile
• Use Interactive Areas
• Make Submissions, post comments, or provide reviews or testimonials
• Submit online forms or make requests for communication or support
• Initiate or complete transactions through the Services
• Initiate or complete credit check applications through the Services
• Make or receive payments
• Send or receive Texts
• Conduct and/or save searches
• Electronically sign agreements
• Communicate with any of the Vroom Representatives
Please note that content posted to the Interactive Areas, including your Submissions posted in such areas, may be publicly viewable or viewable by anyone who uses
the Services. Therefore, if you upload or share any Information to the Interactive Areas, unless otherwise expressly stated by Vroom, such Information may be non-
confidential and may become publicly available. This means that the Information may be collected, used, or redistributed by others, so please proceed with caution
before posting anything sensitive or confidential to the Interactive Areas.
B. Information Collected Automatically
We and certain Third Parties may also automatically collect Non-Personal Information about you and your devices when you interact with the Services. This
Information may include, without limitation:
• Computer or device operating system information
• IP address
• Network information
• Browser type and language
• Connection speed
• Mobile device ID
• Device hardware type
• Referring website or application accessed before or after accessing the Services
• Parts of the Services accessed
• Access times for and length of time spent on a page or using a feature
• Content viewed
• Geographic location
C. Information Collected Through Tracking Tools
When you access our Services, we or Third Parties may use technologies such as “cookies”, local storage capabilities, or other similar technologies to monitor usage of
the Services (“Tracking Tools”). These Tracking Tools allow the collection of Non-Personal Information (such as pages viewed by you within a certain Service and

the duration of the browsing) and PII (such as your login information), including over time and across different properties and devices. Among other things, Tracking
Tools can enable Vroom to automatically activate certain features for you, make your experience on the Services simpler, more relevant and more convenient, and
provide you with personalized, interest-based advertisements, as further described below. Tracking Tools are used widely across the industry.
D. More About Tracking Tools
By accessing the Services, you consent to us setting and accessing Tracking Tools, including cookies, on your device and in the emails we send you, and to tracking
your activities and your use of the Services through these Tracking Tools. For clarity, Third Parties do not have access to Tracking Tools set by Vroom on our Services
except to the extent necessary to help us provide the Services. Vroom and Third Parties may use the following Tracking Tools:
• Cookies: Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website, and may include session cookies (which expire once you close the browser) and/or
  persistent cookies (which stay on your browser and may be used by the browser on subsequent visits to the Services, unless deleted by you). Among other things,
  cookies help us make our Services and your experience better. For example, we use cookies to see which parts and features of our Services are popular, count visits
  to our Services, and improve or tailor the Services and our advertisements to make them more relevant to you. For more information on cookies, click here. You can
  turn off your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, but certain parts of the Services may not work for you.
• Unique Identifiers: We may use unique identifiers to collect information about your use of the Services on an individual basis, such as length of time spent on a
  particular page and pages viewed during a particular log-in period. We use this information to evaluate and improve the Services.
• Web Beacons: Web beacons, or clear GIFs or pixel tags, are small graphic image files that can be embedded in web pages or emails to collect information about your
  use of our Services or the correspondences that we send. The information collected by web beacons allows us to analyze how and how many people are using the
Services or when you open our emails.
• Analytics and Other Technologies: We use other technologies and analytics services, such as Google Analytics, to help analyze how you use the Services and to
  collect and store information, such as how often you visit the Services, what features you use, what pages you visit, what emails you open, and what other sites or
  applications you used prior to and after visiting the Services. We use this information to improve our Services. These services may use cookies, including first party
  and third-party cookies, as well as other Tracking Tools. For example, Google Analytics uses cookies to inform, optimize, remarket, and serve ads based on
  your visits to the Services. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Service is subject to the Google
  Analytics’ Terms of Use and Google’s Privacy Policy. You may find additional information about Google Analytics here. You have the option to opt out of Google’s
  use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page here or the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on here. Alternatively, you can opt out of certain
  cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page here.
• Mobile Device Identifiers: Mobile device identifiers are stored on your mobile device and track how you use the Services through your mobile device. Mobile device
  identifiers enable collection of Non-Personal Information (such as usage and traffic data). As with other Tracking Tools, mobile device identifiers help Vroom learn
  more about your preferences and internet behaviors in order to operate and improve the Services.
E. Transferring Information Between Jurisdictions
The Services are hosted in the United States and are mainly directed to residents in the United States. We currently only buy and sell vehicles in the United States. If
you are accessing the Services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that
differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Services, you are consenting to the transfer of your PII to the United States.
You consent to such transfer by agreeing to this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms.
4. Vroom’s Use and Sharing of Information
    Generally, we use and share your Information to provide our Services, to improve our Services, and to send you news about promotions, products, or services
    offered by us or our Business Partners.
A. To Provide the Services
We use the Information collected, and may share such Information with Third Parties to provide, operate, and maintain our Services, including for the following
purposes:
• Personalizing, improving, and operating our business and the Services
• Better understanding the needs and interests of you and others who may use the Services
• Fulfilling requests you make related to the Services, including to respond to your support requests or to process and facilitate
  transactions conducted on the Services
• Processing and facilitating payments
• Providing Service announcements or providing you with further information, recommendations, and offers from us or Third Parties
• Complying with applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena, or governmental requests, or other legal obligations

• Resolving disputes or security or technical issues
• Enforcing our agreements, including this Privacy Policy or the Terms, or investigating potential violations thereof
• Protecting, investigating, and deterring against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized or illegal activity, or otherwise as we believe to be necessary to protect the rights,
  property, or safety of Vroom, the Vroom Representatives, you, or the general public
• Performing statistical analysis and research activities
• Processing or storing Information through Vroom’s affiliated companies and authorized Third Parties, as reasonable for business
  purposes (including, as applicable, their affiliates as necessary to provide us with the requested services)
• Other commercial purposes (including, without limitation, offering you insurance, financing, service contracts, or other products in connection with the purchase or
  sale of a vehicle)
If we share your PII for a purpose not mentioned in this Privacy Policy, we will receive your express approval prior to the disclosure.
B. Marketing and Advertisements
We may use your Information to send you information about our Services or the services of our Business Partners, including new products and promotions.
Additionally, we may provide your Information to our Business Partners to contact you directly about their products and services, if we think you would be interested.
Some advertisements may come from Third Parties called “ad networks.” Ad networks may include ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors, and research
firms. We do not provide PII to any ad networks for use not related to the Services. In some cases, advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to
those who fit a certain general profile category or may be based on information inferred from the Information provided by you, your Services usage patterns, or your
activity on Third Party services, including over time and across properties and devices. By using the Services, you consent to us providing you with marketing materials,
which may include the following:
• Direct Marketing: Communications or advertisements sent directly to you by Vroom or our Business Partners via telephone, mail, email, text, or other methods for
  the purpose of offering you products or services that may interest you.
• Advertisements: Advertisements and commercials from us or Third Parties. Note that if you click on any Third-Party advertisements, you may be transferred to a
  website of the Third Party or receive other messages, information or offers from the advertiser and/or other Third Parties, and these advertisers and/or Third Parties
  may use their own Tracking Tools to collect information in order to send you advertisements and for their legitimate business interests.
• Interest-Based Advertisements: Content and advertisements personalized to your interests, which are inferred from your activity on our Services and other sites and
  services, and based on information gathered by us or Third Parties using Tracking Tools. These advertisements may be served to you on our Services or other
  services, sites, or apps. To learn more about interest-based advertising, and to opt-out of collection and use of your information for interest-based advertising, please
  click here to opt-out of collection and use by Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) participating companies and here to opt-out of collection and use by NAI member
  companies. For mobile opt out, please visit the NAI Mobile Choices page here, or download the Ghostery mobile application.
You may withdraw your consent to receive marketing materials by following the opt-out instructions for removing yourself from our mailing list that is made available
in the commercial materials transmitted to you. Furthermore, we give you the ability to opt out of marketing-related emails by clicking on a link in each such email.
Please note that even if you choose to remove your Information (opt out), you will still see advertisements while you’re browsing online, however they may be less
relevant to you and your interests. Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from
your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive. Please note that if you opt-out of
targeted advertising, we may still track your use of the Services for analytics, operations and security purposes.
C. Uses and Disclosure of Non-Personal Information
Non-Personal Information informs us how you interact with the Services. Some of this Information may be derived from PII, but, if so, we anonymize or aggregate the
PII so that it does not identify the individual from whom it was derived. Non-Personal Information enables us and Third Parties we authorize to figure out how and how
often you engage with different parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them. We may use Non-Personal Information for:
• Industry analysis
• Marketing and advertising
• Facilitating collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services
• Fighting spam/malware
• Other business purposes (e.g., by reporting on trends in the usage of our Services)
Vroom may transfer and disclose Non-Personal Information to Third Parties at its own discretion.

5. Third Parties
    Who we have in our passenger seats...
We may share Information with Third Parties, and they may share Information with us. Unless we tell you differently, our Service Providers do not have any right to PII
that we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us or provide products or services requested or accessed by you. You consent to our sharing of
Information, which may include PII, with Third Parties, such as, without limitation:
• Social media networks
• Payment processors
• Credit check and financing Service Providers
• Vehicle inspectors
• Vehicle history providers
• Shipping providers
• Web hosting services
• Analytics and advertising Service Providers
• Sales management tools
• Marketing and promotion partners
• Law enforcement or other legal authorities or bodies pursuant to a subpoena or court order; however, if permitted, we may allow you an opportunity to object to the
  subpoena or court order before we provide the requested Information
  Some specific Third Parties include, without limitation:
• Microsoft Azure, whose privacy policy can be found here
• Google Analytics, whose privacy policy can be found here and here
• RouteOne LLC, whose privacy policy can be found here
• PayPal, whose privacy policy can be found here
• Stripe, whose privacy policy can be found here
• Redstone Payments Solutions, LLC, whose privacy policy can be found here
• Capital One, whose privacy policy can be found here
• Facebook, whose privacy policy can be found here
We use commercially reasonable efforts to engage with Third Parties who share our commitment to protecting your Information, and who post a privacy policy
governing their collection, processing and use of information. However, we do not control these Third Parties and are not liable for their practices, products, or
services. Please read their terms of use and privacy policies to better understand their privacy practices. Please note that some Third Parties who receive your
Information may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
6. More About Financial Information
    All about the Benjamins: The Information that helps you get either your dream car, or a chunk of change for your no-longer-dream car.
If you make a purchase or sale through the Services, or otherwise use the Services in a way that involves sending or receiving payment, we may request Information to
process and complete the transaction such as:
• Credit card information
• Name and contact information of financial institution
• Account type
• Routing number
• Account number
This Information is collected and stored by our third-party payment processing companies, which may include PayPal, Stripe and RedStone Payment Solutions, LLC
(the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. We may,
from time to time, request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the following purposes:
• Completing transactions you initiate through the Services
• Enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate
• Protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent transactions
• Otherwise as needed to manage and operate our business

If you fill out a credit application through our Services, we may collect and store your credit application details that are eventually shared with Vroom’s Business
Partners or Service Providers, such as, without limitation, RouteOne LLC or Capital One, and which may contain some or all of the following Information:
• Name
• Email address
• Mailing address
• Phone number
• Date of birth
• Driver’s license number
• Employment information
• Income information
By submitting your Information, you expressly authorize (i) Vroom to transfer such Information to its Business Partners or Service Providers, and (ii) Vroom, and any
of its Business Partners or Service Providers, to use that Information in accordance with their respective privacy policies.
7. Ways to Limit our Information Collection and/or Use
    Here are some ways you can limit the Information that we collect and/or use from you. And don’t forget your privacy road flare if you have any questions:
    support@vroom.com
If you want to limit our collection and/or use of your Information, you have several choices, including:
• Limiting Information provided to Vroom: You can always opt not to disclose certain Information to us; however, if you choose not to provide us with certain
  Information, you may not be able to access certain features or services.
• Terminating your Account(s): You may be able to limit our collection and use of some of your Information by terminating your Account(s) on the Services.
• Your choices for Tracking Tools: You can opt-out of collection by certain Tracking Tools as described in the section titled “Marketing and Advertising”. Most
  browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive or from your device, block acceptance of cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is
  stored. You may also be able to erase or disable other Tracking Tools using the settings of your browser or mobile device. However, please note that if you block or
  erase Tracking Tools then our Services (and your experience) may be limited.
• Do Not Track: Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services that you
  do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. We do not support Do Not Track requests at this time.
  Furthermore, we can’t and don’t make any promises about how Third Parties react when you set this signal on your browser.
8. Accessing Your Information
If you are registered, you can access Information associated with your Account by logging into the Services.
California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of
personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates
and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Vroom, Inc., Attn:
General Counsel, 1375 Broadway, 11th Floor, New York, NY 10018.
9. Deleting or Modifying Your PII
We hope our road trip together doesn’t end any time soon, but if for any reason you wish to close your Account or delete or modify your PII, you can email
support@vroom.com, and we will make reasonable efforts to submit to your request, subject to applicable laws, rules, regulation, or court order. Please note that
unless you instruct us otherwise, or as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we may retain and use Information collected from you after termination of your Account, for
as long as reasonably required, for the purposes of which such Information was collected, including, without limitation, for future analytics and analysis, in order to
comply with our legal or business requirements or obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy, and/or to enable you to reinstate your
Account, all as permitted under any applicable privacy laws. Furthermore, public activity on your Account prior to deletion may remain stored on our servers and
may remain accessible to the public. Aggregate and/or anonymous information derived from your Account and/or use of the Services may remain on our servers
indefinitely.

10. Our Commitment to Data Security
We take reasonable physical, managerial and technical measures to maintain the security and integrity of your Information and the Services and prevent
unauthorized access or use through generally accepted industry standard technologies and internal procedures, which include:
• Taking reasonable steps to verify your identity when you log-in to your Account and/or our Services, such as requesting a unique
  password. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and Account information at all times.
• Maintaining PII behind secured networks and facilities that is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special
  access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential.
• Encrypting sensitive financial information, such as credit card information, via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology prior to
  transmission over the Internet.
• Implementing a variety of industry standard security measures and tools, including, for example, the use of Microsoft Azure Cloud
  servers.
Please note, however, that there are inherent risks in transmission of information over the Internet or other methods of electronic storage, and we cannot guarantee
that unauthorized access or use of your PII will never occur. We will not be responsible or liable for unauthorized access, hacking, or other security intrusions or the
theft, deletion, corruption, destruction, damage, or loss of any data or information.
11. Changes to the Privacy Policy
Vroom reserves the right to make changes to its Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason, so please re-visit this page frequently. If Vroom makes a material
change to the Privacy Policy, then Vroom will notify you either by email or by posting a notice on the Services. If Vroom, in its reasonable discretion, believes that
any part of this Privacy Policy must be amended in order to comply with any legal requirements, the amendments may take effect immediately or as required by law
and without any prior notice. All changes are effective as of the date indicated at the top of this page (“Last Updated”), and your continued use of the Services after
the indicated date will constitute acceptance to be bound by those changes.
Vroom reserves the right to stop, temporarily or permanently, the operation of any and all Services without notice, at any time. All information (ours or yours) made
available on the applicable portion of the Services may be removed or deleted, so please make your own copy of any Information you submit to Vroom. Vroom will
not be liable to you or to any third party for any changes, suspension, or discontinuance of the Services or any malfunctions that may occur in connection thereto.
12. Children’s Privacy
We do not intend to and do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of thirteen (13). We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that
we can verify that children under the age of thirteen (13) are not using the Services. Please email us at support@vroom.com if you have reasons to suspect that we
collected PII from a specific child under the age of thirteen (13).
13. Business Transfers
In the event that there’s a “merge ahead” (that is, if we choose to buy or sell assets), your Information is typically one of the transferred business assets.
Additionally, if we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your Information would be one of the assets that is
transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your
Information, including your PII, as set forth in this policy.
14. Interpretation
The section and paragraph headings in this Privacy Policy, as well as all summaries included in this Privacy Policy, are for convenience only and shall not affect the
Privacy Policy’s interpretation. Any use of “including”, “for example” or “such as” in this Privacy Policy shall be read as being followed by “without limitation” where
appropriate.
15. Any Questions?
Congratulations -you’ve reached the checkered flag for this Privacy Policy. Thanks so much for keeping your hands on the wheel and your eyes on the road. If you
have any questions, please email us at support@vroom.com.
